【The fate that cannot be liberated】
【无法解脱的命运】
[Episode 8]
[第8集]
Do you understand what I'm saying?
你明白我说的话吗？
Bring the teapot. I want to drink.
拿茶壶来。我要喝水。
I am He Jiuling.
我是何九龄。
At least you can understand my actions today.
至少你能理解我今天的举动。
Worth celebrating.
值得庆祝。
Put on your shoes. The ground is cold.
穿上你的鞋子。地面很冷。
shoe.
鞋。
Miss,
女士，
I've brought you what you want.
你想要的东西我已经带来了。
This is the sweet potato you want.
这是你想要的红薯。
Your food is almost gone
你的食物快吃完了
And you still give your best to strangers.
而你仍然把最好的东西 给陌生人。
Everyone who comes is a guest.
每个来的人都是客人。
Moreover, these two people are very pitiful.
而且，这两个人还很可怜。
We should treat them well.
我们应该善待他们。
You are so kind. I'm leaving now.
你真善良。我现在就要走了。
careful.
小心。
here. Eat a sweet potato.
这里。吃一个红薯。
Thank you ma'am.
谢谢夫人。
This is my husband.
这是我先生。
He's like your boyfriend. He didn't speak either.
他就像你的男朋友一样。 他也不说话。
Your husband looks very strong
你老公看起来很坚强
and have the ability to work.
并有工作能力。
He is different from my boyfriend
他和我男朋友不一样
People who are unable to speak and are physically weak.
不能说话且身体虚弱的人。
But he's nice to you.
但他对你很好。
Eat it yourself.
自己吃吧。
I know how to use a spoon.
我知道如何使用勺子。
I have never seen a couple as devoted as you two.
我从来没有见过像你们两个这样忠诚的情侣。
Maybe your father doesn't have enough insight into men.
也许你父亲 对男人的洞察力不够。
It doesn't matter whether a person is strong or not.
一个人强不强并不重要。
The important thing is that he is good to the people he loves.
重要的是 他对他爱的人很好。
There is such a young master
有这样一个少爷
Lowering my dignity to take care of you
为了照顾你而降低自己的尊严
You are lucky.
你很幸运。
If that's not enough for your father to let you marry him
如果这还不足以让你父亲 让你嫁给他
He must be blind.
他一定很盲目。
Let me give you a suggestion.
我给你一个建议。
Stay at my house for a few more days
在我家多住几天
Don't go back until you two have had your baby.
在你们两个生完孩子之前不要回去。
unnecessary.
不需要。
We'll leave tomorrow.
我们明天就出发。
We are going to visit a relative.
我们要去拜访一位亲戚。
Is this relatively reliable?
这样相对可靠吗？
Don't worry.
不用担心。
That relative will definitely take us in.
那个亲戚肯定会收留我们的。
Can't you just keep feeding me?
你就不能一直喂我吗？
give me a break,
让我休息一下，
You can?
你会？
Eat it yourself.
自己吃吧。
I can eat it myself. look.
我自己可以吃。看。
When you eat by yourself, you are normal.
当你自己吃饭时，你是很正常的。
But you feed me like a pig.
但你却像喂猪一样喂我。
Madam, this is our gift to thank you for letting us stay.
女士，这是我们感谢您 让我们留下来的礼物。
No, I can't accept that.
不，我不能接受。
I'm just letting you stay for one night.
我只是让你住一晚。
I didn't do anything else.
我没有做任何其他事情。
I can't accept that much money.
我不能接受这么多钱。
Take it.
拿着吧。
Please buy me some casual clothes.
请给我买一些便服。
I'll finish it after the meal.
饭后我会把它完成。
Take care of each other on the road and live well.
路上互相照顾 ，好好生活。
Thank you ma'am.
谢谢夫人。
Then we left.
然后我们就离开了。
careful.
小心。
Be good. Don't run around.
乖一点。别乱跑。
Master Rong?
容大师？
Master Rong!
荣师傅！
Master!
少爷！
Miss He?
何小姐？
Why are you dressed like this?
你为什么穿成这样？
you? ? ?
你？？？
You must have mistaken me for someone else.
你肯定把我误认为是别人了。
Please do not follow us. I am afraid.
请不要关注我们。我害怕。
Are you scared?
你感到害怕？
You kicked me too hard just now
刚才你踢我太狠了
You still said you were afraid?
你还说你害怕？
You've exposed yourself, okay?
你已经把自己暴露了好吗？
Miss He, so
何小姐，所以
The person next to you must be Master Rong.
你旁边的人一定是容大师。
no doubt.
毫无疑问。
I've been drawing pictures of him for many years. I can't be wrong.
我画他的照片 已经很多年了。我不会错的。
Oh, heaven.
哦，天堂。
Master Rong finally woke up!
容大师终于醒了！
Master Rong, Master Rong.
荣师傅，荣师傅。
Is he really a fool now?
他现在真的是个傻子吗？
My livelihood!
我的生计！
I can't sell books.
我不会卖书。
I feel bad.
我心疼。
He will always be the master of star selection.
他永远是选星大师。
When I take him to Wuhua Mountain, everything will be fine.
等我带他去五华山， 一切就都好了。
Then let's go.
然后走吧。
Why are you crawling around here?
你为什么在这儿爬来爬去？
Didn't you notice they were searching everywhere?
你没注意到 他们正在到处搜寻吗？
Looking for you?
正在寻找你吗？
He is the young master of Xingxiang Pavilion
他是星象阁的少主
and His Majesty's favorite minister.
以及国王陛下最喜爱的大臣。
I guess the capital is probably in chaos now.
我猜现在京城大概已经乱了。
Even this small city has checkpoints.
即使是这个小城市也有检查站。
But, but, aren't you already married?
但、但是，你们不是已经结婚了吗？
No one believes you can save him.
没有人相信你能救他。
he and I? ? ?
我和他？？？
forget it.
忘了它。
Just follow him for now.
暂时关注他吧。
I'm going to the post office to see if there's any hitchhikers.
我要去邮局 看看是否有搭便车的。
Your hand is hurt. I'll ask.
你的手受伤了。我去问问。
that's it.
这样就可以了。
Then asked them if there was a carriage to Shidu.
然后问他们 有没有去十渡的马车。
if not,
如果不，
Ask them if they have a carriage to go
问他们是否有马车去
Mengze in Jiangling or Xinze Lake in Guizhao.
Mengze in Jiangling or Xinze Lake in Guizhao.
The carriage to Jiangling Mengze must be very big.
到江陵蒙泽的马车 一定很大。
Master Rong is in poor health.
容师傅身体不好。
But if it’s a carriage going to Guizhao Xinze Lake ,
但如果是去贵照新泽湖的马车 ，
It must be small.
它一定很小。
There were too many officers and soldiers along the way.
一路上官兵太多了。
If we are recognized on the road
如果我们在路上被认出来
We're done.
我们完成了。
If none are available, ask them if they have any—
如果没有可用的， 就问他们是否有——
stop. Just ask yourself.
停止。你去问问你自己吧。
I'll stay and take care of him.
我会留下来照顾他。
All right.
好吧。
Master.
少爷。
I'll go find some water.
我去找点水。
We're out of water.
我们没水了。
I need to buy some.
我需要买一些。
T. Looking for water?
T、去找水？
Wait for me here, okay?
在这里等我，好吗？
I'll get you a steamed bun to eat.
我去给你拿个馒头来吃。
steamed stuffed bun?
包子？
I'll be back when you finish eating.
等你吃完我就回来。
Thanks.
谢谢。
I'll add some seasoning powder for you.
我给你加点调味粉。
Come, get the bread.
来，拿面包。
Take good care of him.
好好照顾他。
We have the same bread.
我们有同样的面包。
Why do you smell so good?
为什么你的味道那么好闻？
Star Reaching Master,
摘星大师，
It's an honor to spend time with you so close.
很荣幸能与您 如此近距离地共度时光。
Although the timing is not right,
虽然时机不对，
I'd like to introduce myself. I am -
我想自我介绍一下。我是 -
You are a pig.
你是一头猪。
- goodbye. careful. - goodbye.
- 再见。小心。 - 再见。
(Feiyun Inn) Be careful. Don't slip.
(飞云客栈) 小心点。不要滑倒。
gentlemen,
先生，
Is there a carriage to Gangneung and Mengze?
有 去江陵蒙泽的马车吗？
If not I can rent one.
如果没有的话我可以租一个。
I'm not sure myself.
我自己也不太确定。
Why don't you go in and ask our boss?
你为什么不进去问问我们老板呢？
Thanks.
谢谢。
please come in.
请进来。
Is there a carriage from Jiangling to Mengze?
江陵有去蒙泽的马车吗
or Guizhao?
or Guizhao?
I'll rent it if you want. I don't mind the cost.
如果你愿意，我就租它。 我不介意费用。
L-Rongye--
L-荣爷--
Where did you take Yu?
你把宇带到哪里去了？
???Drink the blues? ? ?
??? 喝一杯忧郁？？？
??? Where love brews into pain? ? ?
??? 爱在其中酝酿成痛苦？？？
???Can’t wait for the dark night? ? ?
??? 等不及黑夜了？？？
??? Accompanied by flickering candlelight? ? ?
??? 伴随着摇曳的烛光？？？
I won't let you hurt him again
我不会再让你伤害他了
I will never let you go.
我绝对不会放你走的。
???I am no longer as impetuous as I was when I was young? ? ?
??? 我不再年少时的浮躁？？？
???I heard you were somewhere across the water? ? ?
??? 听说你在水对岸的某个地方？？？
???I want to swim upstream? ? ?
??? 我要逆流而上？？？
??? Enjoy the ups and downs of the journey? ? ?
??? 畅饮旅途中的酸甜苦辣？？？
??? Lament the waste of life? ? ?
??? 感叹生命的浪费？？？
???Drink the entangled thoughts? ? ?
??? 喝下纠缠的思绪？？？
???Get drunk, is it so difficult to meet you? ? ?
??? 喝醉吧， 遇见你这么难？？？
??? Let’s drink to the sadness, shall we? ? ?
??? 让我们为悲伤而干杯吧？？？
??? Gray hair, laughing at me Troubled dreams? ? ?
??? 头发花白，笑我 苦恼的梦？？？
??? After we spent so many days together, I can't forget you? ? ?
??? 我们在一起度过了这么多天之后，我无法忘记你？？？
Rong Yu!
Rong Yu!
??? Lament the waste of life? ? ?
??? 感叹生命的浪费？？？
???Drink the entangled thoughts? ? ?
??? 喝下纠缠的思绪？？？
Let me go!
让我走！
??? Gray hair, laughing at me Troubled dreams? ? ?
??? 头发花白，笑我 苦恼的梦？？？
??? After we spent so many days together, I can't forget you? ? ?
??? 我们在一起度过了这么多天之后，我无法忘记你？？？
??? Enjoy the ups and downs of the journey? ? ?
??? 畅饮旅途中的酸甜苦辣？？？
Rong Yu!
Rong Yu!
???Drink the entangled thoughts? ? ?
??? 喝下纠缠的思绪？？？
???Get drunk, is it so difficult to meet you? ? ?
??? 喝醉吧， 遇见你这么难？？？
??? Let’s drink to the sadness, shall we? ? ?
??? 让我们为悲伤而干杯吧？？？
??? Gray hair, laughing at me Troubled dreams? ? ?
??? 头发花白，笑我 苦恼的梦？？？
??? After we spent so many days together, I can't forget you? ? ?
??? 我们在一起度过了这么多天之后，我无法忘记你？？？
Jiuling.
Jiuling.
Thank you for sending my daughter home.
谢谢你送我女儿回家。
- Tell Master Rong that I can't see him today. - Are you hurt? How are you?
- 告诉荣爷我今天见不到他了。 - 你受伤了吗？你还好吗？
I will apologize to him personally tomorrow.
明天我会亲自向他道歉。
General He,
何将军，
My master said it was not necessary.
我师父说没这个必要。
He also said that people from the He family should not come to Rongfu again.
还表示何家的人 不要再到荣府来了。
What?
什么？
You're not injured, are you? your hands? ? ?
你没有受伤吧？你的手？？？
Why are your hands tied?
你的手怎么被绑住了？
Zong Ming, call the doctor.
宗明，叫医生来。
The Rong family does not want Rong Yu to go to Mount Wuhua.
荣家不希望荣玉 去五华山。
No matter what, you insist on taking him away.
无论如何，你还是坚持要带他走。
I don't care about Rong Yu.
我不关心容宇。
but if something happens to you
但如果你出了什么事
How will my father and I get through this?
父亲和我该如何度过难关？
enough. Fortunately she's back.
足够的。幸好她回来了。
I must say.
我必须说。
Didn't you hear what that man just said?
你没听到那人刚才说的话吗？
He said: "People from the He family should not go to Rong Mansion again."
他道：“何家的人， 不要再去荣府了。”
Let’s see what Jiang Rong did.
再看看蒋蓉是怎么做的。
Rong Yu was still unconscious, so he gave us an engagement gift.
容宇还昏迷不醒， 他给我们送了订婚礼物。
Is he still human?
他还是人吗？
Is the Rong family worth your risk?
荣家值得你 这样冒险吗？
Qiuting.
Qiuting.
Father.
父亲。
In fact, Rong Yu was already awake.
事实上，容羽已经醒了。
Really?
真的吗？
That's good news.
那是好消息。
Jiuling,
Jiuling,
Although you are a bit reckless,
尽管你有点鲁莽，
You end up with a good result.
你最终得到了一个好的结果。
You should be happy about this.
你应该为此感到高兴。
I want to live a happy life.
我想过得开心点。
But I am not happy at all.
但我却一点也高兴不起来。
- Jiuling. - Jiuling!
- Jiuling. - Jiuling!
Jiuling!
Jiuling!
Master, Master, you can't go out.
少爷，少爷，你不能出去。
Master, you can't go out.
少爷，你不能出去。
Master.
少爷。
You can't go out.
你不能出去。
Yong adult,
容大人，
I am ashamed.
我很惭愧。
The young master’s current situation
小少爷现在的处境
This is something I rarely see in my life.
这是我一生中很少见到的事情。
So I can only try to prescribe a few medicines,
所以我只能尝试着开几个药方，
Hopefully they can make him better.
希望他们能让他变得更好。
So is he this kind of person?
那么他就是这样的人吗？
Stupid?
愚蠢吗？
He doesn't remember anything.
他什么都不记得了。
But why does he only remember her?
但为什么他只记得她？
Why does he want her?
他为什么要她？
Why must it be her?
为什么一定是她？
Lord Rong, this is not difficult to understand.
容大人，这也不难理解。
Newborn ducks and goslings
刚出生的鸭子和小鹅
Will stick to the first person
会坚持第一个人
They watch.
他们看。
The young master’s current mental state
小少爷现在的精神状态
Just like a newborn baby.
就像刚出生的婴儿一样。
When he was conscious, Miss He was the only one around him.
当他有意识的时候， 身边只有何小姐一个人。
He naturally thinks that she is the closest person to him
他自然认为她是最亲近的人
Feeling uneasy if she wasn't there.
如果她不在场，就会感到不安。
The people closest to you? ? ?
最亲近的人？？？
This will make the Rong family fall out.
这可是要让荣家翻脸的
upside down.
倒挂。
Master, Master, you can't go out.
少爷，少爷，你不能出去。
Yes.
是的。
Master, you can't go out.
少爷，你不能出去。
I'll go back to the Imperial Medical Bureau to discuss it with everyone.
我先回太医局 和大家商量一下。
I'll take my leave first.
我先告辞了。
Master, you can't go out.
少爷，你不能出去。
Master, please stop.
少爷，请停下来。
Master? ? ?
少爷？？？
The young master woke up.
少爷醒了。
Heshan, did you hear that?
鹤山，你听到了吗？
future,
将来，
You are still his bodyguard.
你仍然是他的贴身侍卫。
thank you for your kindness.
谢谢你的好意。
But I can't forgive your betrayal
但我无法原谅你的背叛
A member of the Rong family.
荣氏家族的人。
crime
罪
It's my responsibility alone.
由我一人承担。
Leave a decent person behind
留下一个正经人
By the young master's side.
在少爷身边。
Master, I have something to ask you.
师父，我有件事想请教一下。
Yu, here.
宇，这里。
Let's eat.
我们吃饭吧。
Take these.
拿这些。
OK Catch them.
好的。抓住他们。
Yu, this soup is your favorite.
宇，这汤是你最喜欢的。
here.
这里。
Come.
来。
Have some soup.
喝点汤。
Do you want to eat steamed buns?
你想吃包子吗？
here.
这里。
Come one
来一个吧
Eat it.
吃了它。
Doesn't it taste good?
味道不好吗？
Someone!
有人！
gentlemen.
先生。
Tell the kitchen to make bread when possible.
告诉厨房 尽可能做面包。
return,
还，
Go outside and buy a variety of bread in the city.
到外面 去买一个城里的各种面包。
go.
去。
Sir, the bakery only does business in the early morning.
先生，面包店只做 清晨生意。
Then bring those bakers back to make bread here.
然后把那些面包师带回来在这里做面包。
Give them double wages.
双倍工资给他们。
Do you need me to teach you?
需要我教你吗？
I'm on my way now.
我现在正在路上。
At.
于。
Master!
少爷！
sorry.
对不起。
you're awake. That's great.
你醒了。那太棒了。
Rong Yu!
Rong Yu!
Jiuling!
Jiuling!
your hands!
你的手！
Your left hand is just your support hand.
你的左手只是辅助手。
Don't rush to exercise it yet.
先别急着去锻炼它。
Martial arts practitioners should not rush for success.
习武者 不可急于求成。
I don't.
我不。
Don't you want to become stronger?
你不渴望变得更强吗？
But now you're too eager.
但现在你太急切了。
Even if you can use a sword now,
就算你现在能用剑，
I can beat you with my bare feet.
我赤脚就能打败你。
What's wrong with wanting to become stronger?
想要变强有什么错呢？
future,
将来，
No one can hurt anyone in front of me.
没有人可以伤害我面前的任何人。
No one can take anyone away from me.
没有人可以把任何人从我身边夺走。
I know.
我知道。
you do not know.
你不知道。
Ten years in Wuhua Mountain,
在五华山的十年，
My master and senior brother protected me.
我的师父和师兄保护了我。
You will protect me when I come back.
当我回来的时候，你们会保护我。
But I can't protect anyone.
但我无法保护任何人。
Didn't you say before that you are the best in the world?
你之前不是说过 你是世界上最好的吗？
That's just nonsense.
那只是无稽之谈。
Don't use it against me.
别用它来对付我。
Meet me at the training ground
在训练场见我
Tomorrow morning, let's go exercise.
明天早上，我们去锻炼吧。
Can you get up on time?
你能准时起床吗？
I can.
我可以。
If you really want to learn martial arts
如果你真的想学武术
We won't pamper you like we would at home.
我们不会像在家里那样纵容您。
I don't need to indulge.
我不需要纵容。
(To disciple Jiuling)
（致弟子九灵）
I have a deep hatred for Xingxiang Pavilion.
我对星象阁有着深仇大恨。
Therefore, the life and death of the people in that place have nothing to do with me.
因此，那个地方的人的生死 与我无关。
I will soon leave the mountains and travel.
我很快就要离开大山去旅行了。
Don't come to me.
别来找我。
What kind of ancient history does it have?
有着什么样的古老历史
Can my master be allowed to harbor such hatred?
能让我的主人怀有这样的仇恨吗？
It must be painful.
一定很痛苦。
Must I make my master give up her hatred?
我必须让我的主人放弃她的仇恨吗？
For the mistakes I made?
为了我犯的错误？
Senior brother, there is something wrong with amnesia.
师兄， 失忆出了问题。
After taking it,
服用后，
Not only did Rong Yu not sever emotional ties,
容羽不仅没有断绝感情联系
But it also hurt mentally.
但精神上也受到了伤害。
I need a prescription for an antidote.
我需要处方来配制解药。
I hope to get a reply soon.
我希望尽快得到答复。
Free blood vine grass and dragon head ginseng
送血藤草 和龙头参
I quickly found Jia Lin.
我很快就找到了家琳。
Your Highness,
殿下，
These are healing treasures
这些都是治愈的宝藏
You have found it for our king.
你已经为我们的国王找到了。
It took you two years
你花了两年时间
Finally got a foothold.
终于站稳脚跟。
Now, we are at the point where the king is re-electing his successor.
现在，我们正处于国王重新选择继承人的时刻。
So please don't do this.
所以请不要这样做。
Hurry to Jialin. This matter need not be discussed any further.
赶紧去嘉林吧。 这件事不必再讨论了。
please come in.
请进来。
OK
好的。
this way please.
这边请。
How is it going?
最近好吗？
Healing treasure.
治愈之宝。
careful.
小心。
hurry up!
快点！
Hold steady. And thrust!
持稳。还有推力！
Miss, are you also here to see the young master?
小姐，您也是来看少爷的吗？
I'm afraid you're here in vain.
恐怕你是白来了。
Something happened to the young master recently.
最近少爷出了点事。
He hasn't been out for a while.
他已经有一段时间没有出去了。
There used to be a lot of people waiting here
以前有很多人在这里等候
Just to take a look at him.
只是为了看他一眼。
But things have changed.
但事情已经改变了。
Even my tea stall business has declined.
就连我的茶摊生意也下滑了。
Can you make me a pot of tea?
你能给我泡一壶茶吗？
OK
好的。
I also heard
我也听说
He seemed to have become a fool.
他似乎变成了一个傻瓜。
He couldn't eat or speak.
他不能吃东西，也不能说话。
However, you still like him.
然而，你还是喜欢他。
You're the only person I've seen in a while.
你是我这段时间唯一见过这样的人。
He is not a fool.
他不是傻子。
Well, he's not.
好吧，他不是。
Fool.
笨蛋。
What an idiot.
真是个白痴。
The last time my father and I were here, he was just staring at a bun.
上次我和父亲在这里的时候， 他只是盯着一个包子看。
This time we came and he was still staring at the pancakes.
这次我们来了， 他还盯着煎饼。
Don't you think he looks like the same person?
你不觉得他很像一个人吗？
He looks just like the dog you fed bread to last time.
他看起来就像你上次喂面包的那只狗。
Exactly.
确切地。
You also noticed his gaze, right?
你也注意到了他的目光吧？
Yes, the eyes are exactly the same.
是的，眼神一模一样。
I was going to throw a stone at him
我本来打算拿石头砸他的
While the two guards were not paying attention.
趁着两个侍卫不注意的时候。
I want to see if he really can't speak
我想看看他是不是真的不会说话
Or dodge.
或闪避。
Who hit me?
谁打我了？
Your nose is bleeding. How are you?
你的鼻子在流血。你还好吗？
- Sir, do you need me to wipe the blood for you? - Who hit me?
- 先生，需要我帮你擦血吗？ - 谁打我了？
Who wants your damn rag?
谁想要你那该死的抹布？
- How are you? - who is it?
- 你还好吗？ - 是谁？
is her.
是她。
go.
去。
you? ? ?
你？？？
H-He Jiuling.
H-He Jiuling.
Did you throw a stone?
你扔石头了吗？
Tell me, did you throw a stone?
告诉我，你扔石头了吗？
NO, I have not. The guards in the mansion were watching closely.
不，我没有。府邸内的侍卫们 都在密切注视着。
This is just my idea.
这只是我的想法。
I didn't really throw it.
我真的没有扔。
Ouch, it hurts. Miss He! Miss He!
哎呀，好痛。何小姐！何小姐！
Give me a steamed bun.
给我一个馒头。
OK
好的。
Miss He, what do you want to do?
何小姐，你想做什么？
Here, miss.
在这里，小姐。
This is the bun I gave you. Eat it.
这是我送给你的包子。吃了它。
Eat it with gratitude.
怀着感恩的心吃它。
Eat it.
吃了它。
Eat it now.
现在就吃吧。
eat.
吃。
He Jiuling, we want to stand up for you.
何九龄，我们是想为你出头的。
Your Majesty has granted him your marriage.
陛下已将您的婚姻授予他。
But now he has become a fool.
但现在他却变成了一个傻子。
How does he deserve you?
他怎么配得上你？
What does it have to do with you?
跟你有什么关系？
if you keep talking nonsense
如果你一直胡言乱语
Next time I will give you more than just a piece of bread.
下次我给你吃的就不仅仅是一个面包了。
YY-you? ? ? You are lawless.
YY-你？？？你无法无天。
Have you forgotten the fate of the young master?
难道你们忘记了少主的命运吗？
- Sir, should we stop this? - Everyone, get out!
- 先生，我们应该停止这一切吗？ - 大家都出去吧！
They came here under the pretext of visiting the sick to see the spectacle.
他们以探望病人为借口来到这里看奇观。
I can't teach them a lesson.
我无法教训他们。
Let her hit them.
让她打他们吧。
gentlemen,
先生，
The young master is not in good health.
少爷身体不太好。
The buns are broken.
馒头坏了。
Buy more.
买多点。
Yes.
是的。
Miss He.
何小姐。
Did Rong Yu???
Did Rong Yu???
your face? ? ?
你的脸？？？
nothing.
没什么。
How could there be nothing?
怎么可能什么都没有呢？
Is it all because of me? ? ?
都是因为我？？？
I need to go back.
我需要回去。
The young master is not in a good mood.
少爷心情不太好。
He hardly slept or ate.
他几乎不睡觉也不吃饭。
All he does is stare at the bun all day long.
他所做的就是整天盯着发髻。
I'll add some seasoning powder for you.
我给你加点调味粉。
I'll be back when you finish eating.
等你吃完我就回来。
I think I know why he stopped eating.
我想我知道他为什么不吃饭了。
I'll go and buy.
我去买。
Miss He.
何小姐。
Can I go visit the young master?
可以去拜访一下少爷吗？
No, I won't go.
不，我不会去。
I can't bring anyone else down.
我不能连累其他人。
Don't worry.
不用担心。
No one will be punished again.
没有人会再次受到惩罚。
Master.
少爷。
Master, go this way.
少爷，这边走。
Master, please slow down.
少爷你慢点。
slowly.
慢慢地。
Come.
来。
Take your time, Master.
慢慢来，少爷。
Master, look!
少爷你看！
???Under the sunset at dusk? ? ?
??? 黄昏夕阳下？？？
???I traveled thousands of miles to a distant place? ? ?
??? 我千里迢迢去远方？？？
???Playing the piano under the moonlight? ? ?
??? 月下弹琴？？？
???These drinks won’t make me forget? ? ?
??? 这些饮料不会让我忘记？？？
???The desire I wrote for you? ? ?
??? 我写下的对你的渴望？？？
??? Our destiny is written on paper? ? ?
??? 我们的命运是写在纸上的？？？
??? Like the strongest wine? ? ?
??? 就像最烈的酒一样？？？
??? There is no way to escape fate? ? ?
??? 命运无路可逃？？？
???Looking back, I saw you waiting? ? ?
??? 回头一看，我看到你在等待？？？
???Our life is full of joy and sorrow? ? ?
??? 我们的生活充满欢乐和悲伤？？？
??? Desire to crystallize into a bright galaxy???
??? 渴望结晶 成明亮的银河???
???You quietly turned around and closed the marriage certificate? ? ?
??? 你悄悄转身 合上了婚书？？？
???Ask how many stars are there in the sky? ? ?
??? 问天上有多少颗星星？？？
???The desire I wrote for you? ? ?
??? 我写下的对你的渴望？？？
??? Our destiny is written on paper? ? ?
??? 我们的命运是写在纸上的？？？
??? Like the strongest wine? ? ?
??? 就像最烈的酒一样？？？
??? There is no way to escape fate? ? ?
??? 命运无路可逃？？？
???Looking back, I saw you waiting? ? ?
??? 回头一看，我看到你在等待？？？
???Our life is full of joy and sorrow? ? ?
??? 我们的生活充满欢乐和悲伤？？？
??? Desire to crystallize into a bright galaxy???
??? 渴望结晶 成明亮的银河???
???I gently caress the guzheng, waiting for passers-by like you???
??? 我轻轻抚着古筝， 等待着你这样的路人???
???So you are my indissoluble bond? ? ?
??? 原来你就是我的不解之缘？？？
???Under the sunset at dusk? ? ?
??? 黄昏夕阳下？？？
???I traveled thousands of miles to a distant place? ? ?
??? 我千里迢迢去远方？？？
???Playing the piano under the moonlight? ? ?
??? 月下弹琴？？？
???These drinks won’t make me forget? ? ?
??? 这些饮料不会让我忘记？？？
???The desire I wrote for you? ? ?
??? 我写下的对你的渴望？？？
??? Our destiny is written on paper? ? ?
??? 我们的命运是写在纸上的？？？
??? Like the strongest wine? ? ?
??? 就像最烈的酒一样？？？
??? There is no way to escape fate? ? ?
??? 命运无路可逃？？？
???Looking back, I saw you waiting? ? ?
??? 回头一看，我看到你在等待？？？
???Our life is full of joy and sorrow? ? ?
??? 我们的生活充满欢乐和悲伤？？？
??? Desire to crystallize into a bright galaxy???
??? 渴望结晶 成明亮的银河???
???You quietly turned around and closed the marriage certificate? ? ?
??? 你悄悄转身 合上了婚书？？？
???Ask how many stars are there in the sky? ? ?
??? 问天上有多少颗星星？？？
???The desire I wrote for you? ? ?
??? 我写下的对你的渴望？？？
??? Our destiny is written on paper? ? ?
??? 我们的命运是写在纸上的？？？
??? Like the strongest wine? ? ?
??? 就像最烈的酒一样？？？
??? There is no way to escape fate? ? ?
??? 命运无路可逃？？？
???Looking back, I saw you waiting? ? ?
??? 回头一看，我看到你在等待？？？
???Our life is full of joy and sorrow? ? ?
??? 我们的生活充满欢乐和悲伤？？？
??? Desire to crystallize into a bright galaxy???
??? 渴望结晶 成明亮的银河???
???I gently caress the guzheng, waiting for passers-by like you???
??? 我轻轻抚着古筝， 等待着你这样的路人???
???So you are my indissoluble bond? ? ?
??? 原来你就是我的不解之缘？？？